Guide to the Elizabeth Bishop Papers, circa 1880-2023 (bulk 1929-1979)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES XVI. PHOTOCOPIES AND REPRODUCTIONS
  - Boxes 86-96, 98 (Photocopies) (PR Box 10)
  - Box 97 (Photocopies) (PR Box 11)
  - Boxes 99, 103-104, 112 (Photocopies) (PR Box 12)
  - Boxes 101-102 (Photographic reproductions) - Elizabeth Bishop's slides of Brazil (PR Box 13)
  - Boxes 113-116 (Photocopies) (PR Box 14)
  - Boxes 118-122 (Photocopies) (PR Box 15)
  - Boxes 123-127 (Photocopies) (PR Box 16)
  - Extra Copies of Poems (Photocopies) (PR Boxes 17-20)
  - Photographs, negatives, and postcards (Photocopies) (PR Box 21)
  - Correspondence from Elizabeth Bishop to Marianne Moore (Photocopies), [SEE Marianne Moore Papers, Rosenbach Library and Museum, Philadelphia, PA for originals] (PR Box 22)